Yograj Dhage

Web/HTML Developer

Mobile: +91-9763674385

Email: - Yograj.dhage@gmail.com

Portfolio link:- https://yograjdhage1.github.io/profile/



HIGHLIGHTS

14 years of professional experience in E-learning/UI/Web/WordPress Development & Website/Graphic Design Industry.

Websites, Web/Mobile Applications, UI Designing/Development as per Web 2.0 Standards and W3C Standards.

Excellent command on HTML4/5 creation, CSS3, Responsive Design, Bootstrap, Sass, SVN, Git, UI Designing, Mobile Apps & Cross-Browser Compatibility. Involved in creation of various dynamic sites & content management system (CMS) based designs. Also have expertise on entire Adobe Creative Suite.

Involved in various projects based on online Tool storyline and Rise tool.

Great passion of creativity, interests in learning new things, good grasping power. Always ready for adventures and challenges, quick in grasping new things.

- UI development for Websites, Web applications.
- Cross browser compatibility like IE, Mozilla, Safari, Chrome.
- Involved in design Integration with developer
- Responsive web development (RWD) for phones, tablets, desktops
- Web Debugging Tools Firebug, IE Developer Toolbar, Chrome Dev Tools
- An expert in Elementor plugins used in WordPress.
- PSD, XD, Figma to HTML
- HTML to WordPress
- Replication or copying of the Website
- Website design from scratch
- Theme setup and design customization

EDUCATION

- □ Batchelor of Commerce (B.Com.) from Maratha Wada Mitra Mandal College affiliated to University of Pune in 2004.
- Successful completion of 'DIM (Diploma in Multimedia) From Arena Multimedia.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Articulate Rise · HTML5 · Bootstrap · Figma · Sass · Material-UI · CSS Flexbox · Adobe XD · Front-End Development

· Responsive Web Design· JavaScript · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · Reactjs · WordPress with elementor plugins

YOGRAJ DHAGE

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

OWLSystems Solutions Pvt LTD (Remote)

December 2023 - Till date (5 month)

OWLSystems Solutions Pvt Ltd OFFSHORE

https://owlsln.com/owlsln/

Role: As a front-end developer, I prefer to do the PSD to HTML conversion. As a WordPress UI designer/developer. I have been instrumental in creating the look, feel, and functionality of various websites. My responsibilities include designing and developing websites as per PSD to HTML as the WordPress designer converts them and then I do css fixes.

Current Projects:-

- 1. https://test-vra.pantheonsite.io/
- 2. https://test-indian-rocks-beach.pantheonsite.io/
- 3. https://www.kopernikglobal.com/
- 4. https://test-eccrffa.pantheonsite.io/
- 5. https://dev-pinole.pantheonsite.io/
- 6. https://www.nixa.com/

(Username: - digital and password: - deployment)

Environment: HTML 5, Bootstrap, sass, Gutenberg-wordpress, Photoshop, VS Code, Json, Jquery, Javascript etc.

Client: - https://www.planeteria.com/ (US)

Website and Wordpress Developer

May 2022 - Till date

Self-employed

Online profile :- https://yograjdhage1.github.io/profile/

Role: Responsive UI HTML Designing, WordPress Development and Implementation & I am now working as a freelancer and have worked with some domestic clients I am sharing this below.

Current Project: -

- A. https://rungila.com/en/
- B. http://tssa.in/
- C. https://asamegacart.com/
- D. https://davikalogistics.com/

Aptara New Media (Pune)

December 2013 - May 2022 (8.5 Years)

APTARA NEW MEDIA P LTD OFFSHORE

http://www.aptaracorp.com

Role: Responsive UI HTML Designing, Development and Implementation & Ipad compatibility.

Responsibilities:

- Involved in requirement gathering.
- Compatible interfaces in web format using CSS and HTML, XHTML.

Environment: Photoshop, VS Code, Json, Jquery, Javascript etc.

Client: - KPMG, Philips, Deloitte, pwc, EY, Infosys.

Current Project: - In Client Infosys CODE OF CONDUCT AND ETHICS and worked an Reactjs, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.

ClearPoint Interactive Health Education Pvt. Ltd (Pune)

July 2010 - Nov-2013 (3.4 Years)

CLEARPOINT LEARNING SYSTEM P LTD OFFSHORE

http://www.clearpointlearning.com

All Project Description:

LMS-Portal works to implement & run the e-training/e-education/e-learning initiatives of an organization. Based on different needs of educational institutions and business groups LMS-Portal provides a segment specific elearning & distance education platform for a **University, School/College, Tuition Class, Training Institute & Corporate.** The focus of LMS-Portal is to have an e-learning platform that is segment specific, conveniently scaleable to changing needs and is quick to implement.

Role: UI HTML Designing, Development and Implementation & Ipad compatibility.

Responsibilities:

- Involved in requirement gathering.
- □ Compatible interfaces in web format using CSS and HTML, XHTML.

Environment: Photoshop, Dream weaver, Integration

Signure Technologies Pvt. Ltd (Pune)

May '09 – June 2010 (1.1 Year)

SIGNURE TECHNOLOGIES P LTD OFFSHORE

https://www.explara.com/

Project Description: Explara is an event and venue management portal. The portal home page shows venue, event listing. Venue Owners can add/manage venues, venue manager, and venue customer support to get business. Users can post/manage events and view events, view venues, invite people for joining an event, also can book a venue for an event. Event organizer can add tickets to their events which are shown for online purchasing.

Role: UI Designing, Development and Implementation

Responsibilities:

□ Involved in requirement gathering.

□ Compatible interfaces in web format using CSS and XHTML.

Environment: Photoshop, Dream weaver, Integration with PHP etc.

Project: https://www.explara.com/

Harbinger Knowledge Products Pvt. Ltd (Pune)

July 08 - April 09 (8 Months)

HARBINGER KNOWLEDGE PRODUCTS PVT LTD OFFSHORE

http://www.harbingergroup.com/

Project: www.raptivity.com

Role: Creating Simulations, Creating Intro, & Interface Design

Responsibilities:

Preparing Layouts.

Creating Graphic User Interfaces (GUIs).

□ Creating Simulations.

□ Creating Intro Animations

Environment: Flash, Photoshop, Dreamweaver, etc.

DETAILS

Current Designation:	Web/HTML/WordPress Developer
Previous Company:	Aptara New Media Pvt Ltd.
Profession:	Diploma in Multimedia Professional
Date of Birth:	04/02/1982
Marital Status:	Married
Mailing Address:	407-A River View dangat patil nagar shivane Pune – 411023.
Telephone:	9763674385
Email:	yograj.dhage@gmail.com